allowed to go play in my backyard and
and play in front of family and friends
and people who've watched and supported
me my entire life.
>> What do you feel you most add to this
defense?
>> I feel like I had a a different level of
versatility. Um I feel like there's
nothing on the football field I I can't
do. I haven't shown that I'm able to do.
You know, you know, shown I can cover. I
can come down the box and play the run
very well. I, you know, can get the ball
and bring it back to our sideline. um
with with the turnovers I produce and
just, you know, position flexibility and
versatility. You know, I played, you
know, snaps at, I think, every position
on the field and and done a multitude of
jobs. And I think that it's something
that I pride myself on and something
that, you know, helps it team become
very effective.
>> Thank you.
Uh Liam,
>> hey Nick. Uh I saw that you grew up in
the DC area and I saw a tweet from you
after the Caps won the Stanley Cup just
talking about how surreal that was. Did
you have a favorite DC area athlete
growing up?
>> Uh I was always a a Commanders or back
then the Redskins. I was I was a
Redskins fan through and through. You
know, Shawn Taylor and Clint Porter is
my f my two favorites. Um, you know, I
wanted to play running back and safety
because of those two. And, you know,
they were they were two guys who were
very important, very pivotal pieces on
those those commanders commanders teams
back then and people who uh had a lot of
success and worked hard and did what
they were supposed to.
>> And you played with Cam Bayham in Indie.
He obviously over overlapped with Donte
Jones in Minnesota. Did he tell you
anything about what to expect from
Dvonte Jones's coaching or scheme?
>> I haven't talked to Cam about it. I'm
sure, you know, I'll reach out to him in
the next couple days just to, you know,
get a feel. But, you know, meeting with
Dante, a great guy, al also a DMV, a DMV
guy. Um, we have a little high school
rivalry there. Uh, he claims that, you
know, he's had some success against
Damata. I can't envision any, you know,
McName Mustang having any success
against the Mata, but um, you know, at
the end of the day, real down to earth.
You know, definitely someone who knows a
lot of football and, you know, knows his
stuff and, you know, I can't wait to be
coached by him.
>> Thanks, Nick. Scott,
>> I love those WCAC rivalries. Good to see
you again, Nick. Coverage you on Friday
nights uh with the Mata. Uh welcome to
Washington again. Um you mentioned Shawn
Taylor. I can't imagine what this is
like for you full circle. Obviously, you
grew up idolizing a Shawn Taylor and now
you're playing his position for the team
you cheered for and rooted for as a kid.
What is What is this like emotionally
for you knowing what Shawn meant to you
growing up?
Uh, it's a it's a lot. Um, you know what
I'm saying? I feel like, you know, you
never it still hasn't hit yet that, you
know, I'm coming home to play in in DC
is actually it's it's pretty crazy, but
you know, someone I always watch growing
up. You know, I have a couple of his,
you know, jerseys in my in my house um
and whatnot. But just someone who I
always idolize um someone who I always
watch, someone who I always wanted to be
like. And you know, it's it's a a very
surreal, very, you know, humbling thing
to know that, you know, coming back home
to a team that I've rooted for. You
know, I know, you know, guys on Twitter
have pulled up some of my old tweets
from when I was younger, you know,
tweeting away, you know, as a fan. And,
you know, I feel like they know that,
you know, I was in the mud with them.
You know what I'm saying? I I
definitely, you know, live in the D with
with the Commanders and, you know, it's
definitely fun to know that I'm playing
for a team that, you know, I root for, a
lot of my friends root for and, you
know, it just gives that a little extra
motivation to go out there and and play
uh play harder as well.
>> You know, Nick, you know, dating back to
your Damata days, you always played with
physicality that carried to Maryland and
obviously in the NFL. take me through
that mindset of of being that physical
safety that you don't mind go coming up
there and blitzing or stopping the run.
>> It's always something, you know, at the
end of the day, I always say football
still boils down to being able to impose
your will on somebody else. If you know,
if if you you have to win your
one-on-one match up every play and, you
know, if you win your one-on-one matchup
more than the other guy does, you know,
I think you're you're in um you're in
tune for a pretty successful day. So,
it's just, you know, at the end of the
day, I pride myself on just being able
to go down there and dominate anybody
who's in front of me. Um, to go down
there and just, you know, be a game
recorder and help, you know, impact the
team and help, you know, help my team
win in any way, shape, or form. So, you
know, again, you know, Sean was a very
big, very physical physical player and,
you know, again, I pride myself on being
able to, you know, play like that. And,
you know, also like some of the other
safeties I grew up watching, you know,
Brian Dawkins and the the Bob Sanders
and whatnot. So, you know, just the guys
that grew up watching, you know, I kind
of try to emulate what they did.
>> Good to see you again.
>> You, too.
>> David.
>> Hey, Nick. Congrats and welcome home.
Uh, I want to kind of build off the fan
conversation. Obviously, you've been on
one side of this fan base, you know,
economy or or environment as as I should
say. Being on this side of the fan
interaction dynamic, what are you
expecting? What are you already uh
experiencing from that? Uh, it's
definitely a deep fan base. Um, you
know, I've always known that DC fans are
are are rider, true ride or die. You
know, at the end of the day, I used to
always say no matter what happened, you
know, the week before, what happened the
season before, I was always want to be
like, yeah, you know, they do this, they
do that, they going to make the playoffs
and we going to, you know, be happy in
Washington. So, you know, at the end of
the day, it's one of those things where
there's a a childlike optimism that, you
know, a lot of fans have, and it
definitely is something that I think
drives the drives the players and drives
the community um to continue to, you
know, fight and continue to play and
play hard for the for the fans and the
people who support us. Um, so, you know,
being a fan and, you know, being around
people who are always fans, um, you
know, we had our rough days for sure,
but it was definitely, um, it's
definitely fun. It's like all right,
like you know, now I'm on the other
side. It's like, okay, like, you know,
you got to give the fans something to
cheer for, something to hope for, and
something to be able to be prideful
about. And then for for you and to go
from competing against each other, but
for the same team, Maryland, competing
against each other in the AFC South, and
now back to competing against each other
at practice to make each other better
for the same team. How does that feel?
>> It feels good. You know what I'm saying?
I was getting my deal done and he, you
know, I'm getting my phone blowing up
and I see, you know, Chico Conco signs
to Washington. I almost started
laughing. You know what I'm saying? Cuz,
you know, for the past, ever since we
met, it's like we haven't been able to
separate from each other. So, you know,
whether it's playing against him in the
in the AFC South where, you know, I
always tell him that, hey, like, you
know, I won the majority, we won the
majority of those of those battles. But,
you know, at the end of the day, just
coming back and being teammates like we
were at Maryland. Um, and being able to
compete against each other is is it's a
dream come true. And you know, I love
competing against Ch. Great tight end,
you know, fast, got run great routes,
super competitor, so we definitely go
after get after it.
>> Thanks, Nick.
>> Donna,
>> hey, Nick. Uh, welcome to Washington.
Uh, you says you grew up as a
Washington, uh, fan and everything. So,
when they were looking at you to come to
Washington, what was the main selling
factor for you to say this team fits you
best?
I think it's, you know, for one, it's
just the ability to play play at home,
play for a play for a team that I grew
up rooting for. Um, I've heard nothing
but great things about Dan Quinn. Um,
you know, great, you know, true players
coach. Um, and whatnot. Um, one of my my
mentors and my former high school coach,
Josh Wilson, you know, he speak spoke
very highly of Dan Quinn and, you know,
also man, he played for the Commanders,
too. So, it's, you know, it's one of
those things where, you know, me and him
joke a lot. It's like, you know, our our
careers kind of mirror each other and
very and you know, almost it's almost
scary how how similar our careers are.
Um, but, you know, it's definitely those
things and then at the end of the day,
you know, going in and trying to help
revamp a defense and and go out there
and be successful, you know, you're
always up for a challenge at the end of
the day. And as people get to know you
here in Washington, being back home and
your teammates, what is it? What is it
that you want them to know most about
you, who you are overall?
>> Uh, I would say, you know, for one, you
know, I'm a believer in the Lord. You
know, at the end of the day, as as one,
and, you know, at the end of the day,
I'm going come in, I'm going work hard.
I'm going be a professional about what I
do. um come in early, stay late, and
just, you know, try to be a leader um by
example, you know, and bring some of the
the other guys along and, you know, go
out there and play hard and practice
hard for for my teammates, for the city,
for the fans so we can go out there. At
the end of the day, it's about, you
know, we're in the business of winning,
and that's all I care about is winning
football games. So, whatever we got to
do, whatever I got to do to make sure
that happens, what's going to happen?
>> That's how you say welcome back home.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> All right. Thanks, Nick. Appreciate it.
>> No problem. Appreciate you.
>> Thank you.